Jakub Imiołczyk

Front-End Developer



Personal Info

Email

jakub.imiolczyk@yahoo.com

Phone

795 881 926

GitHub

https://github.com/Prime153

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/jakub-imiołczyk

Website

https://jakubimiolczyk.gatsbyjs.io/

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

SCSS

React (Router, Redux)

Gatsby

Material UI

Git

Styled Components

MJML

High personal Culture

Team communication

Resistance to stress

Creativity

Assertiveness

I am a graduate of a technical school with an IT profile. My goal is to become a front-end developer. Soon I am going to part-time studies focused on my current field. I have been learning new technologies for over 1.5 years. I feel very comfortable in React technologies and I'm not afraid to get to know new ones. I am a creative person, a fast learner, and like to work in a team.

Work History

2018-01

Freelancer

- present

Koszecin

Performing local IT orders in the Koszęcin commune. Installation of systems. Repair and assembly of desktop computers. System bug fixes.

2020-07 - 2020-08 **IT Support**

Energy-24, Koszęcin

- Working with Microsoft Office
- Repair of local system errors

2019-10 - 2019-11

IT Support Trainee

Viplex. Rozwiązania informatyczne, Lubliniec

- Solving local IT orders
- Installation of computer systems
- Implementation of systems for Comarch ERP Optima companies
- Assembling desktops according to customer needs

2018-01

Viplex. Rozwiązania informatyczne., Lubliniec

- 2018-02

Education

2017-09

Zespół Szkół Ogólnokształcąco-Technicznych, Lubliniec

- 2021-04

Major: IT Technician

Projects

Reptile Planet

This project was created for two reasons - the desire to learn more about React Redux and the combination of my main interests. The website layout was designed by me in Figma. All product data and the shopping cart itself have been embedded in the Redux state. This way you can easily manage your data from anywhere in the application. When placing an order, you can check the current weather in the location specified by the user via the OpenWeatherMap API.

Solar System

My first React project. This is a website for a solar energy company. The website was created in the "One Page Scroll Site" convention. The React Router Hash Links library was used here to support smooth traffic between subpages. In the "Calculator" subpage, I implemented a simple calculator that calculates how many kW should be installed to reduce the monthly cost of electricity given by the user. AOS Animations Library was used for the scrolling animation.

Kanban Board

Languages

English - C1

Hobby

Programming, Technologies, Terraristics, Paleontology

A simple application made in React. It uses the Beautiful DnD Library to smoothly move cards. When creating a new card, the user can specify a priority.

Hamster Smasher

It is a simple pure JavaScript game. It was created in order to practice my skill in this language. The user has to hit the cursor with the hamsters that appear from time to time. The game is over when the user reaches the allotted number of points or loses all lives. Before starting the game, you can choose the difficulty level. The game creates data as you select a level.

Portofolio

My first project in Gatsby.js. The GSAP library for animation has been implemented here. I also used the CSS framework, Material UI. On the "contact" page, I used the EmailJS API to send an e-mail to my own account. For the images on the page, the "Gastby-image" plugin was used.

Courses

Frontend Masters (Complete Intro To Web Development, Getting started with JavaScript, CSS Grids and Flexbox for responsive Web Design, Advanced CSS Layouts, Complete Intro To React V6)

Eduweb (React from the Basics, React in Practice, Gatsby.js Course

YouTube channels (Joma Tech, Ben Award, Hello Roman, Brian Design, Web Dev Simplified)

Certificates

Diploma confirming Qualifications EE.08 Installation and operation of computer systems, peripherals and networks

Diploma confirming Qualifications EE.09 Programming, creating and administering websites and databases